<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_descr">
		<text>A compound of several hollow organic formations, this artifact emits a gaseous substance that can neutralize chemical or toxic particles inside the body without harming it. Because of its effectiveness, this artifact is in great demand. Warning: Because of its organic nature this artifact is well known to spontaneously combust more so then any other organic artifact and it is not advised at all to wear this artifact when near a flame or acidic anomaly.  This artifact has many other negative properties, such as greatly enhancing the effects of Psy-waves and fields projected by Mutants as well as anomalies.  Some stalkers have had the effects of the Psy-waves so amplified while wearing one or more of these artifacts that they have simply screamed in anguish like a wounded animal and then doubled over dead  because of the effects of the  of the psy-fields being enhanced by the artifact. This artifact should also never be worn when entering an electric anomaly, as it will conduct the electricity and increase the amps of the electric current. Stalkers also complain that they feel as if their energy is being sapped rite out of their body and they can feel their willpower faltering when equipping this artifact. Many stalkers have also been known to faint when equipping this artifact as they lose all strength in their legs.  Another redeeming quality of this artifact however is that it will heal a person’s wounds and lacerations very quickly. Thus this artifact can be sued to speed up wound healing when standing idle or when crouched behind cover during a fight. Radiation output is HIGHEST on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/2 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_baloon_name">
		<text>Bubble</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_descr">
		<text>A reddish formation of compressed fossilized plants, soil and animal debris. Can partially neutralize chemical poisons. Quite widespread and not very effective. This artifact will catch fire when it is near an open flame, fire or even spontaneously combust when it is in close proximity to a very warm environment.  This artifact will also aggravate acidic burns when its user is exposed to any type of acid. This artifacts organic nature does however allow it to absorb chemical and toxic elements and thus gives its user protection in a toxic and hazardous environment by reducing the toxicity in its user’s bloodstream.  Another downside of this artifact is that it will increase the effects of Psy-wavelengths and also is very conductive in the presence of electricity.  It will also add a drained effect to its user when contact is made to the users skin or is even within close proximity to its users body. The Stone Blood will however speed up wound recovery due to its organic nature. It sells well to hippies outside of the Zone. Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/20 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_blood_name">
		<text>Stone Blood</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_descr">
		<text>This artifact is formed in anomalous zones with intense thermal activity. Actively consumes excessive heat, remaining cool to the touch throughout. This artifact will also protect the user against acidic burns found in toxic chemical anomalies. This (crystal) artifact is not brittle but instead hard as diamond. It has a relatively heavy weight as it is very dense. Then exposed to the presence of chemical or toxic environment this artifact will however increase the corrosive effects of the chemical and toxic environment. Thus a stalker will struggle to use this artifact in chemical, or environments with a high toxicity level. It also conducts electricity strangely enough, as it seems to react in a conductive way when exposed to electrical current.  Another positive effect that this artifact has is that when coming into the presence of a human or organic body it will reduce bleeding as clotting will occur throughout the body. (It is not recommended to keep this artifact in your possession for too long as blood clots can be hazardous to your health.) This artifact is also highly sought after by jewelers outside of the zone as the inner core of this artifact is not radioactive. It is only the first 1cm of its outer layer that emits radiation. Once the inner core has been refined exquisite jewelry can be made out of this artifact. Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/4 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_descr">
		<text>This artifact looks like a sapphire stone got squashed between melted cheeses. The inside of the artifact when polished shines like Sapphire. This artifact is very dense and as hard as sapphire. The inside of this artifact is sometimes used by jewelers to make jewelry. Interestingly enough during the cutting of the radioactive artifact and after the refinement of the artifacts blue sapphire like material the finished product doesn’t contain any radiation. Only the yellow, outer shell appears to give off radiation. The Artifacts hard blue inside is also known to absorb toxicity in the environment while the outer shell is known for being slightly resistant to heat.  Due to its extreme density, this artifact is extremely heavy and is one of the heaviest items in the Zone. Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/6 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_flower_name">
		<text>Stone Flower</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cristall_name">
		<text>Crystal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_descr">
		<text>This artifact offers slightly more Psy-protection than its cousin the Moonlight artifact. The composition of this artifact includes electrostatic elements, but scientists have yet to identify the exact physical conditions required for its formation. The artifact is popular in the Zone and valued by its residents and visitors for its energizing properties, although it can tire the body out through prolonged use. This artifact hinders blood clotting however and increases bleeding of open wounds.  This artifact is well known for its ability to protect its user from the dangerous effects of electricity.  It acts as a ground for users and will actually absorb electricity that passes into the user’s body. This artifact is also extremely light and very portable. Radiation output is Low on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] prot. reduction eq. of 1/3 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_battery_name">
		<text>Battery</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_descr">
		<text>This strange artifact was considered useless by many scientists for a long time. Until recently it was discovered that this artifact is indeed quite useful.  It can be described as two blue-colored discs held together by a bluish material in-between the discs. It provided a high amount of Psy protection due to the two halves absorbing the Psy field’s emissions and the gooey part in the middle of the artifact acts as acoustics absorption. This artifact also absorbs electromagnetic interference and acts as a grounding material (Surge protection). Many stalkers have stumbled into an electro anomaly while drunk, while wearing this artifact on their bodies and they have survived being electrocuted.  When the contracting inside of the artifact comes into contact with a person’s flesh, the person will feel rejuvenated and full of energy thus increasing stamina recovery. Many stalkers claim that this artifact can induce a sort of hyperactivity in them.  One downside of this artifact however is that it increases bleeding because it has the adverse effect of reducing blood clots. Useful in the medial practice for people who have many blood clots but bad in military conditions when clotting is needed. This artifact is also extremely light and very portable.  Radiation output is Very High on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] prot. reduction eq. of 1/3 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_dummy_name">
		<text>Shell</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_descr">
		<text>Shaped like a DNA helix, the beads are created in the Burner anomaly and pulsate, generating emissions beneficial to the human body. These emissions increase the metabolism of any living creature, accelerating clotting and healing of open wounds. The exact mechanism behind this artifact continues to puzzle scientists. The artifact also has the beneficial ability to protect the body and materials against flame/acidic damage. However it should be noted that when this artifact is in the presence of toxicity it will immediately increase the damaging effects of the toxin thus leading to a higher corrosion level of equipment and help the toxin rec havoc on the body of living tissue.  Another dangerous side effect of this artifact is the fact that it will increase electricity conductivity, so the danger of electrocution is much higher while wearing this artifact during storms and while wondering electric anomalies.  The artifact is also quite heavy for such a small artifact and thus can weigh a person considerably down. Radiation output is Low on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/2 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dummy_glassbeads_name">
		<text>Mama's Beads</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_descr">
		<text>TThis artifact is very similar in appearance to the moonlight artifact. The artifact is a spherical object that looks very similar to a Plasma Globe or Plasma Lamp.  When worn on the body the artifact is known to slightly counter the harmful effects of Psy-anomalies or Psy-wave lengths that some mutants produce. The flash will absorb electricity when the wearer comes into contact with it. Later the flash will release a static build-up that is usually not deadly to a person or creature, although the effect can be similar to a Taser shock.  When a stalker puts both his hands on the artifact it will cause a similar effect as a Plasma Globe and a stalker will feel energized. The artifact also has the slight disadvantage however as any open wounds or wounds on the users body will not heal at a normal rate and can actually hinder the healing process.  This artifact is also extremely light and very portable.  Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] prot. reduction eq. of 1/6 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_flash_name">
		<text>Flash</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_descr">
		<text>This unique electrostatic artifact can resonate under the influence of Psy-waves. Stalkers have learned to fine-tune the artifact so that it resonates in opposite phase to the main source of emissions, thus significantly neutralizing their effects. This beautiful orb of an artifact also increases electricity protection by reducing conductivity in the body when exposed to high amounts of electricity.  It will also increase energy and stamina recovery because of its unique electric properties allowing its user to feel energetic and lively. An adverse effect, which this artifact has however is that it will increase bleeding and open wounds are slower to heal in the presence of this artifact.  This artifact is also extremely light and very portable. Radiation output is Low on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] prot. reduction eq. of 1/4 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_moonlight_name">
		<text>Moonlight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_descr">
		<text>This semitransparent artifact looks like a bunch of translucent spider webs. It is also consequently quite sticky like spider webs.  It is found in or near electro anomalies. It is a common artifact and is known to be able to smooth fluctuations in electric field density.  When worn on the body the artifact is known to slightly counter the harmful effects of Psy-anomalies or Psy-wave lengths that some mutants produce. It can absorb high voltages of electricity and reduces the damaging effects of electricity on living creatures. Because of its electrical nature and the fact that it is quite sticky it tends to stick to a person when used and gives the great advantage of energizing a person to make them feel lively and energetic although the effect is very minimal. The stickiness of the artifact will also spread to wounds on the body of a living creature and will damage any living tissue.  This artifact is also extremely light and very portable.  Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale. Emits radiation.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] prot. reduction eq. of 1/9 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_electra_sparkler_name">
		<text>Sparkler</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_descr">
		<text>This artifact, which resembles the human eye, considerably increases the body's metabolism, helping wounds heal quicker. Experienced stalkers say that the Eye also brings luck. The effect that this artifact has to a user’s body in high temperature is positive as it reduces the users temperature when exposed to heat as well as cooling the materials within close proximity to it. It will aslo protect against any types or kinds of acids. It neutralizes the ph in acids. This artifact is extremely dangerous when exposed to chemical anomalies as it allows the toxicity to be amplified and will increase its potency. It is not advised to have this artifact on or near a person’s body when exploring the toxic  areas of the Zone, unless you have a death wish.  This artifact is also known colloquially as the “Copper eye” as it will conduct electricity and amplify its dangerous effects/conductivity to organics in the same way as copper does. This artifact is however a godsend when exposed to open wounds. Many stalkers describe how when they have been mauled by a deadly mutant or when they have just experienced massive lacerations to their body that the “Eye” has a ‘magical’ effect on their wounds. Rite before their very eyes the wounds will begin to “knit” itself and rapid clotting will occur to the open bleeding wound. Thus many stalkers have survived after being attacked by mutants when they have run out of bandages. Radiation output is VERY HIGH on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 2/3 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_eye_name">
		<text>Eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_descr">
		<text>This artifact forms in areas of high thermal activity. Produces powerful infrared emissions, which intensify metabolic processes, healing wounds before its bearer's very eyes. As this artifact is very rare, it is extremely valuable. This very valuable artifact is similar to the “Eye” in that it will cool down the users core temperature in the presence of heat and will even cool down materials within close proximity to the user. It also has a high tolerance to Acid and will lend this property to its user. It negates the ph of Acids. While sharing many similar but much more properties with its causing the “Eye” artifact it is also a death sentence to have this artifact on one person when entering a toxic or chemical anomaly. It will aggravate the toxic particles and will enhance the effect of the chemicals as soon as they enter the user’s bloodstream. The artifact is however a miracle when it comes to healing wounds and open cuts, or lacerations. Many Veteran Chimera hunters may have a Flame artifact in their possession in case they get mauled by the Chimera.  It is a legendary artifact in the Zone well known for its healing ability. Many stalkers owe their lives for not bleeding out because they, or a fellow stalker was able to close their wounds and stop major arteries from letting their victims bleed to death.  Radiation output is HIGHEST on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of single kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_name">
		<text>Flame</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_descr">
		<text>It is a spherical artifact made out of a red coloured crystal, created in the Burner anomaly. It has an unique property – it has a constant temperature of 75 degrees Fahrenheit/24 degrees Celsius, regardless of its surroundings. This allows it to absorb heat from the user and creates a little pocket around the user to reduce heat. It will also protect the user from acidic burns. The presence of this artifact in a chemical or toxic environment will however increase the effects of the chemical and toxicity in the user’s bloodstream, so it is unwise to wear it in a toxic environment. I also makes the user vulnerable to electrical currents. This artifact has the positive effect however of healing a person’s wounds as the stable temperature it stays at will actually speed up wound recovery and stem bleeding.  It is quite heavy as it is a very dense formation of crystal. Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/3 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fireball_name">
		<text>Fireball</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_descr">
		<text>A relatively rare artifact which forms in areas contaminated with chemicals, Kolobok is highly valued for its ability to heal most kinds of wounds and stop bleeding in a matter of minutes. For unknown reasons, scientists are spreading rumors among stalkers that the artifact interacts with the bearer's genetic code. Another dangerous side effect of this artifact is the fact that it will increase electricity conductivity, so the danger of electrocution is much higher while wearing this artifact while wondering electric anomalies. While looking similar to a porcupine this artifact will also reduce energy recovery as it is known to prick, and hurt the person carrying it because of its sharp needle like appendages. While being very unpleasant the wounds caused by the needle like artifact will heal very quickly, this does however cause constant pain as well as irritation thus reducing stamina. This artifact will also reduce the ability to protect oneself near Psy type emissions caused by anomalies or mutants as well as reducing the ability to protect oneself near acidic anomalies or flame anomalies, as this artifact is highly flammable.  This artifact, given its birth from toxic chemical anomalies, is well known for its ability to increase the user’s protection against toxicity.  It is also lightweight and not too much of a burden to carry around. Radiation output is Very High on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/3 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fuzz_kolobok_name">
		<text>Kolobok</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_name">
		<text>Firefly</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_descr">
		<text>The result of a “Gravi” artifact morphing into its superior and successor. It was also the scientist named  Sakharov who resides at Yantar who discovered the unique properties of the Goldfish for the first time after a massive blowout/emission hit the Zone.  Sakharov  discovered that this new artifact formed from  three “Gravi” artifacts when sucked into each other’s singularity fields. The Goldfish creates a constant Gravitational singularity field which is contained by it for the most part. However some stalkers have been known to disappear for no apparent reason and all that remains of them is a Goldfish artifact where they last stood/slept or resided. Once again the Russian government is highly interested in this artifact. It is whispered by some Ukrainian Spetsnaz officers that a there are agents in the Zone from the Ministry of Defense of the Russian Federation that broker deals to obtain this rare artifact. The Goldfish artifact provides exceptional Thermal and Acidic protection to its user. Strangely enough this artifact also forms a protective and almost greasy film around its user. However this greasy substance is not flammable but is actually a fire retardant. This greasy film that covers a person as well as their equipment will also protect its user against Acid, found in chemical anomalies. It also offers high toxicity protection when exposed in a toxic environment.  Once again the toxic and chemical agents get absorbed into the anomalies singularity field. It is extremely heavy and is not recommended to be used on long trips into the Zone, for extended periods of time. Radiation output is HIGHEST on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of single kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gold_fish_name">
		<text>Goldfish</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_descr">
		<text>Gravi is formed from metallic substances exposed to prolonged gravitation. This makes it capable of sustaining a gravitational field, increasing gravity. Any weight feels a slight tugging within its close proximity. It was the scientist “Sakharov” who resides at Yantar who first discovered that the artifact Gravi creates a minute Gravitational singularity field in intervals of 30 minutes. This artifact may be extremely helpful to the future of science. Its positive properties outweigh the negative properties completely. The only negative properties that this artifact has are its extreme weight as well as its high radiation level.  It will protect the user from the harmful effects of the flame anomalies found throughout the Zone as well as protecting its user from acid pockets found in chemical/toxic anomalies.  The Gravi artifact also absorbs deadly chemicals and toxins when exposed. These chemicals rather than being absorbed by the artifact and disposed of within its singularity field.  WARNING: Some fear that this artifact may someday be harnessed to form new weapons of Mass Destruction. The Russian Government is on the forefront of researching possible ways to turn/incorporate the Gravi into some kind of weapon/weapons. It is extremely heavy and is not recommended to be used on long trips into the Zone, for extended periods of time. Radiation output is Very High on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 2/3 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gravi_name">
		<text>Gravi</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_descr">
		<text>Also colloquially known as the “Radioactive Snowflake”. At first glance, this artifact resembles a white Kolobok. Some claim that it actually is Kolobok, some of its properties are that it greatly increases exposure to a powerful electric current due to creating its own electric field and absorbing any electricity that passes through the users body. Thanks to its unique properties the artifact can significantly increase the bearer's muscle tone, thus greatly increasing the user’s stamina. At first it was a joke but very soon most Stalkers who owned or who have come across a Snowflake artifact came to know it by its nickname. The “Radioactive Snowflake”. The reason for its high radioactivity is unknown to Scientists. It is however as light as a snowflake and is very easy to carry around. The problem is if you consider having greater endurance and a high protection to electric current while carrying around a prickly radioactive object with you to be a boon or not? It shouldn’t be used for long trips as the radioactivity may cook and liquefy you r insides.  Also the artifact is very sharp and will pierce skin almost as easily as it is to carry a cactus around with you. This causes the very unpleasant and extremely irritating effect of increasing bleeding and opening wounds. The artifact also produces an enzyme that will destroy a lot of your blood platelets. This will cause you to bleed out of most orifices. Radiation output is HIGHEST on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,204,0,51] • %c[0,140,140,140] prot. reduction eq. of 1/2 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ice_name">
		<text>Snowflake</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_descr">
		<text>This gravitational artifact attracts and absorbs toxic/chemical particles, reducing the effects of toxic poisoning on the body. Very common in the Zone and is unofficially used outside the Zone for treating people who have been exposed to hazardous or deadly chemical & toxic agents.  This artifact is quite heavy as the gravitational field seems to increases mass. It will slightly protect its user against heat and acidic damage caused by flame anomalies or by the acidic burns caused by the pockets of acid found in chemical anomalies.  This artifact provides a minimal amount of protection against the toxic and chemical agents found in chemical anomalies.  Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/20 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medusa_name">
		<text>Jellyfish</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_descr">
		<text>This artifact is known to feel squishy and has a texture and feel of stretched skin.  When the artifact is exposed to any type of heat source it will immediately start to smell like burnt or burning flesh.  The artifact will become flammable when exposed to any type of heat source. While no damage results in the artifact when ignited, objects in its vicinity can ignite by heat of the burning Meat Chunk.  The fleshy texture of the artifact has pores on its surface and is known to absorb small amounts of toxicity in the environment. When coming into contact with Psy- type of anomalies or Psy-wave lengths the artifact is known to slightly amplify the effects of the damaging  field to biological material. The Meat Chunk is also known to be a conductor of electricity much like the skin or flesh of a living creature.  This artifact is also well known by Stalkers to make one feel physically drained when used for even short periods. When a person is holding the artifact or comes into contact with the artifact and the user/person is hurt, the Meat Chunk will immediately react in a bizarre way and start to heal the wounded area slowly.  Radiation output is Lowest on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/6 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_mincer_meat_name">
		<text>Meat Chunk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_descr">
		<text>This glowing artifact can generate a local directed gravity field. This increase the mass of the artifact greatly as it is extremely heavy. The artifact is known to provide protection against acidic burns as well as protecting its user against flames and heat. The artifact is very beautiful and can also be used to make jewelry with. Only the outer core of the artifact emits radiation while the inner core of the artifact is completely devoid of radiation. It is however extremely dangerous to break open, or cut opened the artifact as most jewelers discovered in the early days of its existence. It seems to explode when it is cut open to its core. The effect of the blast is equivalent to one pack of C4. Thus most jewelers know that the cutting has to be done by a remote machine in a secluded complex. The artifact will also absorb the toxic and most chemical agents in the environment making it a valuable artifact for artifact hunters, although the amount of toxicity absorbed is nothing spectacular.  It is considered by most stalkers as more of a budget artifact, then a truly valuable artifact. It is however very pretty to view at night near a campfire. Radiation output is Low on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/4 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_night_star_name">
		<text>Night Star</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_descr">
		<text>The soul is a unique organic artifact with properties just as unique. It secretes slimy goo that dramatically increases the recovery rate of bodily wounds. Thanks to its reasonable price and an attractive appearance, this artifact is a valuable collector's item. Because of its organic nature this artifact is highly flammable and should not be carried near a campfire, or most heat sources. It is known to spontaneously combust when exposed to a flame, even as small as an ember from a cigarette or cigar but. The artifact provides a high amount of toxic and chemical protection. It is known to absorb the chemical agents and uses them to secrete its healing goo. The artifact enhances the deadly effects of Psy-waves as well as increasing the dangerous effects of electricity to a person’s body.  The artifact is not very dense and thus is not too heavy. The artifact is known to sap its users energy and it will constantly drain the user until they feel fatigued. It does wonders for healing open wounds however. Radiation output is Low on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/4 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_soul_name">
		<text>Soul</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_descr">
		<text>This bizarrely-shaped artifact appears in places with increased gravitational activity. Acting as a kind of sponge that absorbs chemical and toxic elements, this artifact provides protection from outside toxicity as well as from chemical particles that have already made their way into the body. This artifact while appearing to be almost organic in its appearance is actually more alike to coral then most people think. The artifact is nonflammable unlike most other artifacts appearing to be organic in nature. It provides protection to acidic burns as well as fire and heat anomalies. There is no particular faction that takes great interest in this artifact. It is mostly sold to scientists who study and experiment on/with the artifact and its properties.  It is extremely dense and thus extremely heavy. It is a burden to carry around over long distances.  Radiation output is Low on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/2 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vyvert_name">
		<text>Wrenched</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_compass">
		<text>Compass</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_compass_descr">
		<text>A rare artifact - it's been several years since one was found. The artifact can locate gaps in anomaly fields. It is believed that it can help one traverse the most complex anomaly fields completely unharmed. However, very few know how to handle it properly.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/2 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_oasis_heart">
		<text>Heart of the Oasis</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_oasis_heart_descr">
		<text>This artifact was found at the center of the legendary Oasis. It appears that the Heart is a crystallized plant, which has acquired the healing properties of the Oasis. Unlike the Oasis itself, however, this artifact is extremely radioactive.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of single kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_glass_descr">
		<text>Firefly interacts with fields unknown to science, considerably speeding up regeneration of tissue and organs in living beings, as well as normalizing metabolic processes. This artifact can literally get a badly wounded stalker back on his feet in minutes. Unfortunately, Firefly is extremely rare. Warning: Because of its organic nature this artifact is well known to spontaneously combust more so then any other organic artifact and it is not advised at all to wear this artifact when near a flame or acidic anomaly. It will absorb any and all of the deadly chemicals when/if it enters a person’s bloodstream. It provides the highest amount of protection from Toxicity, more than any other artifact. The firefly seems to secrete its own neutralizing chemical agents to neutralize all sorts of chemicals entering the user’s bloodstream as well as completely negating the effects of most nerve agents. Very valuable to the Military as all Governments as this artifacts will make chemical warfare absolute when its secrets are harvested and used to prevent terrorist attacks when biological or chemical weapons are being used by the terrorists. This artifact does seem to enhance the harmful effects of Psy-fields and wavelengths. It is also very conductive and enhances electricity’s deadliness. It increases electricity’s Ampere. The Firefly artifact will also decrease stamina as well as hindering stamina recovery. It heals wounds very quickly though and can be used while stationary or during fighting while in a fixed, and entrenched position. Radiation output is Very High on the artifact radiation scale.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] artifact\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of 1/20 kevlar layer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_surge_name">
		<text>Surge Suppressor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_surge_descr">
		<text>A small but advanced device that drains electric energy from its surroundings. 
It limits the voltage supplied to a body by either blocking or by shorting to ground high voltages. As it is in fact a very advanced resitor circuit, when attached to an uniform or belt the Surge Suppressor greatly increases electrical resistance of wearer's body. This result in siginificantly smaller current and in consequence reduces energy generated by even massive voltages to survivable scale. In consequence amount it provides significant protection against electricity anomalies in The Zone.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] does not require UPD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_frames_name">
		<text>Aluminium Frames</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_frames_descr">
		<text>A backpack attached to the suit with aluminium frames optimizes your carrying capabilities. The frames are of aluminium, due to its light weight, although there are external parts constructed entirely of plastic that provide flexibility while sprinting. The shoulder straps and hip belt are attached to the frame using webbing slid through the frame to provide an amount of adjustability. This quality design allow the shoulder straps to be adjusted up or down to compensate for various torso lengths. Single set of frames replace the main skeleton of your backpack. One can use more frame kits to further reduce weight of other equipment in his possesion like carrying pouches.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grid_name">
		<text>Titanium grid</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grid_descr">
		<text>A backpack attached to the suit with a titanium grid optimizes your carrying capabilities. The grid is of titanium, due to its light weight, although there are external parts constructed entirely of plastic that provide flexibility while sprinting. The shoulder straps and hip belt are attached to the grid using webbing slid through the frames to provide an amount of adjustability. This quality design allow the shoulder straps to be adjusted up or down to compensate for various torso lengths. This grid replaces the main skeleton of your backpack. One can use more frames or grid kits to further reduce weight of other equipment in his possesion like carrying pouches.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] everyday item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] high quality\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_freon_name">
		<text>Freon emittation module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_freon_descr">
		<text>The freon emittation module is designed to keep your body cooler when surrounded by extreme heat. It emits thick freon cooled air particles that protects you by generating a small vacuum layer around your skin. These particles decreases the temperature slightly in short intervals. The module makes you less vulnerable to electricity due to its outer case's, resistance properties.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] does not require UPD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cooler_name">
		<text>Body Cooler</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cooler_descr">
		<text>The Body Cooler is an electric module designed to keep your body cooler when surrounded by extreme heat. It emits quick electrical impulses that protects you by generating a small vacuum layer around your skin. These impulses decreases the temperature slightly in quick intervals. It does not require water to function. The Body Cooler makes you less vulnerable to electricity due to its outer case's, resistance properties.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] high quality\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] does not require UPD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_name">
		<text>Kevlar body plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kevlar_descr">
		<text>These kevlar plates are shaped for ballistic defeating properties, fitting a wide variety of armouring applications. They are designed to withstand smaller ballistic impacts on the front and back of central torso. A lightweight alternative to the heavy armoured steel plates. Wearing any type of armour plating also protects your suit or armour from general condition degradation. Used by military units the world over.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] single layer of kevlar\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] base equivalent for dam. prot.\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_plates_name">
		<text>Carbon steel plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_plates_descr">
		<text>These steel plates are heat treated and shaped for ballistic defeating properties, fitting a wide variety of armouring applications. They are designed to withstand smaller ballistic impacts on the front and back of central torso. But this protection comes at a price as the thick steel plates are very heavy. Wearing any type of armour plating also protects your suit or armour from general condition degradation. Used by Spetsnaz forces extensively.\n \n%c[0,204,0,51]WARNING:\n \n%c[default]Placing conductive metal plates so close to body decreases overall electrical resistance of user, thus applying this type of protection makes you more vulnerable to electricity anomalies.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] single layer of steel plate\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] dam. prot. eq. of two kevlar layers\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_name">
		<text>Camelbak</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_camelbak_descr">
		<text>A hydration system that consist of a pack that is worn on the back or around the waist which contains a bladder that is filled with water to keep a soldier hydrated. A flexible tube leaves the reservoir and has a mouthpiece at the other end. This model is camouflaged and is integrated on the inside of the suit to protect the system from damage when you are engaged in combat or going prone.\n \n%c[0,204,0,51]WARNING:\n \n%c[default]Placing a canister directly on the armor decreases overal electrical resistance of user's body. For this reason applying the system makes the user more vulnerable to high voltages.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] military item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_iam_name">
		<text>Improvised Application Module (IAM)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_iam_descr">
		<text>Improvised Application Module that filters a small amount of radiation particles emitted from artifacts. This mechanical metal pouch construction is the cheapest way of being able to retrieve beneficial powers from less harmful artifact stones when attaching them to an armoured suit. Shelled active gamma atoms in the iron lid actually neutralises much radiation around the body itself. A cheap alternative to the more reliable AAC and AAM.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] does not require UPD\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_aac_name">
		<text>Artifact Application Container (AAC)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_aac_descr">
		<text>Artifact Application Container that filters a reasonable amount of radiation particles emitted from artifacts. This mechanical alluminium container is a popular way of being able to retrieve beneficial powers from harmful artifact stones when attaching them to an armoured suit. Shelled active gamma atoms in the iron lid actually neutralises much radiation around the body itself. Zone manufactured by Zone scientists who reside in military bunkers surrounding the Zone of Alienation.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] does not require UPD\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_aam_name">
		<text>Artifact Application Module (AAM)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_aam_descr">
		<text>Artifact Application Module that filters a reasonable amount of radiation particles emitted from artifacts. This advanced mechanical module is the most effective way of being able to retrieve beneficial powers from harmful artifact stones when attaching them to an armoured suit. Shelled active gamma atoms in the iron lid actually neutralises much radiation around the body itself. An armour application that signals wealth. Used by most Scientists who need to study artifacts. Designed and manufactured in Ukraine by a government institute who equips scientists embedded in the Zone of alienation.\n \n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] technological item\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] high quality\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] does not require UPD\n%c[0,153,255,255] • %c[0,140,140,140] effectivity of mult. units is stackable</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
